Process A (arrival time 9 ms) 16 CPU bursts (tau 100ms)
Process B (arrival time 18 ms) 21 CPU bursts (tau 100ms)
Process C (arrival time 42 ms) 4 CPU bursts (tau 100ms)
Process D (arrival time 156 ms) 11 CPU bursts (tau 100ms)
Process E (arrival time 134 ms) 55 CPU bursts (tau 100ms)
Process F (arrival time 106 ms) 34 CPU bursts (tau 100ms)
Process G (arrival time 65 ms) 80 CPU bursts (tau 100ms)
Process H (arrival time 11 ms) 83 CPU bursts (tau 100ms)
Process I (arrival time 68 ms) 77 CPU bursts (tau 100ms)
Process J (arrival time 0 ms) 10 CPU bursts (tau 100ms)
Process K (arrival time 7 ms) 13 CPU bursts (tau 100ms)
Process L (arrival time 189 ms) 7 CPU bursts (tau 100ms)
Process M (arrival time 16 ms) 48 CPU bursts (tau 100ms)
Process N (arrival time 122 ms) 31 CPU bursts (tau 100ms)
Process O (arrival time 29 ms) 31 CPU bursts (tau 100ms)
Process P (arrival time 159 ms) 16 CPU bursts (tau 100ms)

time 0ms: Simulator started for FCFS [Q empty]
time 0ms: Process J arrived; added to ready queue [Q J]
time 2ms: Process J started using the CPU for 40ms burst [Q empty]
time 7ms: Process K arrived; added to ready queue [Q K]
time 9ms: Process A arrived; added to ready queue [Q K A]
time 11ms: Process H arrived; added to ready queue [Q K A H]
time 16ms: Process M arrived; added to ready queue [Q K A H M]
time 18ms: Process B arrived; added to ready queue [Q K A H M B]
time 29ms: Process O arrived; added to ready queue [Q K A H M B O]
time 42ms: Process J completed a CPU burst; 9 bursts to go [Q K A H M B O]
time 42ms: Process J switching out of CPU; will block on I/O until time 74ms [Q K A H M B O]
time 42ms: Process C arrived; added to ready queue [Q K A H M B O C]
time 46ms: Process K started using the CPU for 64ms burst [Q A H M B O C]
time 65ms: Process G arrived; added to ready queue [Q A H M B O C G]
time 68ms: Process I arrived; added to ready queue [Q A H M B O C G I]
time 74ms: Process J completed I/O; added to ready queue [Q A H M B O C G I J]
time 106ms: Process F arrived; added to ready queue [Q A H M B O C G I J F]
time 110ms: Process K completed a CPU burst; 12 bursts to go [Q A H M B O C G I J F]
time 110ms: Process K switching out of CPU; will block on I/O until time 1072ms [Q A H M B O C G I J F]
time 114ms: Process A started using the CPU for 56ms burst [Q H M B O C G I J F]
time 122ms: Process N arrived; added to ready queue [Q H M B O C G I J F N]
time 134ms: Process E arrived; added to ready queue [Q H M B O C G I J F N E]
time 156ms: Process D arrived; added to ready queue [Q H M B O C G I J F N E D]
time 159ms: Process P arrived; added to ready queue [Q H M B O C G I J F N E D P]
time 170ms: Process A completed a CPU burst; 15 bursts to go [Q H M B O C G I J F N E D P]
time 170ms: Process A switching out of CPU; will block on I/O until time 402ms [Q H M B O C G I J F N E D P]
time 174ms: Process H started using the CPU for 96ms burst [Q M B O C G I J F N E D P]
time 189ms: Process L arrived; added to ready queue [Q M B O C G I J F N E D P L]
time 270ms: Process H completed a CPU burst; 82 bursts to go [Q M B O C G I J F N E D P L]
time 270ms: Process H switching out of CPU; will block on I/O until time 942ms [Q M B O C G I J F N E D P L]
time 274ms: Process M started using the CPU for 22ms burst [Q B O C G I J F N E D P L]
time 296ms: Process M completed a CPU burst; 47 bursts to go [Q B O C G I J F N E D P L]
time 296ms: Process M switching out of CPU; will block on I/O until time 468ms [Q B O C G I J F N E D P L]
time 300ms: Process B started using the CPU for 106ms burst [Q O C G I J F N E D P L]
time 402ms: Process A completed I/O; added to ready queue [Q O C G I J F N E D P L A]
time 406ms: Process B completed a CPU burst; 20 bursts to go [Q O C G I J F N E D P L A]
time 406ms: Process B switching out of CPU; will block on I/O until time 1968ms [Q O C G I J F N E D P L A]
time 410ms: Process O started using the CPU for 156ms burst [Q C G I J F N E D P L A]
time 468ms: Process M completed I/O; added to ready queue [Q C G I J F N E D P L A M]
time 566ms: Process O completed a CPU burst; 30 bursts to go [Q C G I J F N E D P L A M]
time 566ms: Process O switching out of CPU; will block on I/O until time 1238ms [Q C G I J F N E D P L A M]
time 570ms: Process C started using the CPU for 94ms burst [Q G I J F N E D P L A M]
time 664ms: Process C completed a CPU burst; 3 bursts to go [Q G I J F N E D P L A M]
time 664ms: Process C switching out of CPU; will block on I/O until time 2246ms [Q G I J F N E D P L A M]
time 668ms: Process G started using the CPU for 70ms burst [Q I J F N E D P L A M]
time 738ms: Process G completed a CPU burst; 79 bursts to go [Q I J F N E D P L A M]
time 738ms: Process G switching out of CPU; will block on I/O until time 1050ms [Q I J F N E D P L A M]
time 742ms: Process I started using the CPU for 220ms burst [Q J F N E D P L A M]
time 942ms: Process H completed I/O; added to ready queue [Q J F N E D P L A M H]
time 962ms: Process I completed a CPU burst; 76 bursts to go [Q J F N E D P L A M H]
time 962ms: Process I switching out of CPU; will block on I/O until time 1154ms [Q J F N E D P L A M H]
time 966ms: Process J started using the CPU for 204ms burst [Q F N E D P L A M H]
time 4247ms: Process C terminated [Q I H J N K E B]
time 8522ms: Process L terminated [Q D I P G N E F B J]
time 9024ms: Process J terminated [Q O D K H N]
time 14007ms: Process D terminated [Q I]
time 14548ms: Process K terminated [Q empty]
time 16464ms: Process A terminated [Q I B N G H M]
time 22473ms: Process B terminated [Q H O F]
time 25149ms: Process P terminated [Q G E H N M]
time 32371ms: Process F terminated [Q H]
time 35911ms: Process N terminated [Q H]
time 36171ms: Process O terminated [Q E]
time 50419ms: Process E terminated [Q empty]
time 53366ms: Process M terminated [Q empty]
time 72201ms: Process H terminated [Q empty]
time 75337ms: Process I terminated [Q empty]
time 78350ms: Process G terminated [Q empty]
time 78352ms: Simulator ended for FCFS [Q empty]
